Finding Aid for the Edouard Roditi Papers LSC.0644
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Books from the library of Édouard Roditi.
  - Italo Svevo by Svevo, Livia Veneziani., 1951. (Box 182)
    Edizioni Delio Zibaldone; Trieste. With ER's note, "Copy no. 1 of rare limited first edition."
  - Kallos: oeuvres recentes.., undated (Box 182)
    Nane Stern; Paris. Inscribed to ER from J. Hernandez. Brochure for gallery exhibition.
  - L'ARCHE., 1982. (Box 182)
    no. 306-307. Special issue on Algeria.
  - Lazarus rises by Thorp, Roger., [c 1989]. (Box 182)
    Cloud; [Newcastle upon Tyne]. Cloudforms no. 1. Drawings by Michael Thorp.
  - Der Orientteppich. by Cohen, Mitch., c 1989. (Box 182)
    Self published; s.l. Inscribed on front-free endpaper to ER from the author.
  - Physical poetry by David, C.S., undated (Box 182)
  - Pour Sylvie by Walter, Zoum., 1975. (Box 182)
    [Editions de Beaune]; [Paris]
  - Les proscrits (The unwanted) by Sciuto, Lucien., Fall 1986. (Box 182)
    Photocopy from THE JEWISH REVIEW; London.
  - Racontars de rapin by Gauguin, Paul., [1951]. (Box 182)
    Falaize; [Paris]. With Roditi's note laid in, "First edition of the compete text. very rare. A previous edition has been incomplete and full of errors. E. Roditi."
  - What I did on my vacation. by Cohen, Mitch., 1989. (Box 182)
    Inscribed on verso of front cover to ER from the author.
  - Caliban is calling the tribes together., 1986. (Box 185)
    Broadside printed to celebrate CALIBAN'S first issue. Signed by Edouard Roditi, Maxine Hong Kinston, Wanda Coleman, and others. Caliban; Ann Arbor, Michigan
  - FDAC Acquistions 86 Val de Marne., 1987. (Box 186)
    Poster from Fonds Departmental d'Art Contemporain; [Paris?]
  - Maeght au Centre de Chambord., undated (Box 186)
    Poster for an exhibition of the collection of Adrien Maeght.
  - Le semaines de la marionnette a Paris., 1987. (Box 186)
    Poster from Theatre Paris Villette; Paris
  - Une pointe d'art cru., 1987. (Box 186)
    Poster for an art exhibition at Pavillon des Arts, Paris with works by Joe Fafard, Andre Aubry, Jan de Winter, Michel Jamsin, Oliver Girling, Collette Whiten, Yvon Vandycke, Jamelie Hassan, Mark Prent, Dennis Tourbin.
- Accession LSC-1993-004 backlog material, LSC-1993-004 (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)